Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Sparrow - Many moods of Sparrow, 1972; SR-27814; Sparrow; Mighty Sparrow (Box 69)
          In same jacket as #
          Catalog # BW 1001; A-side Matrix # BW-1001-S1 AMD
        - Spartacus R - Third world war, 1983; SR-29057; Spartacus R (Box 69)
          Catalog # ZMRLP 3; A-side Matrix # MPO ZMR LP 3 A1
          Zara Music Records
        - Speedway Blvd. - Speedway Blvd., 1980; SR-27815; Speedway Blvd. (Box 69)
          Catalog # NJE 36533; A-side Matrix # P AL-36533-1A
        - Spherical Objects - No man's land, 1981; SR-27816; Spherical Objects (Box 69)
          Catalog # OBJ 016; A-side Matrix # OBJ 016 A PAG tone
          Object Music
          England
        - Spider - Between the lines, 1981; SR-27817; Spider (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27818. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DL-1-5007; A-side Matrix # DL-15007-AS PRC R2-1-1 MCA SL
          Dreamland Records
        - Spider - Between the lines, 1981; SR-27818; Spider (Box 69)
          In same jacket as # SR-27817. 2 copies.
        - Spike VST - Shut-up and dance, 1988; SR-27819; Spike VST; Taz Money (Box 69)
          Catalog # HAL 12103; A-side Matrix # HAL-12103-A Busta MF
          Street Art Records
        - Spin Masters - Brothers, 1985; SR-27820; Spin Masters (Box 69)
          Catalog # EB 004; A-side Matrix # EB 004-A L 20868
          Electrobeat Records
        - Spinners - Yesterday, today & tomorrow, 1977; SR-27821; Spinners (Box 70)
          Catalog # SD 19100; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773815-A AA-1 1 PR
        - Spinners - Love trippin', 1980; SR-27822; Spinners (Box 70)
          Catalog # SD 19270; A-side Matrix # 0-1-SM1-3 STA-804481-E SP SG
        - Spinners - Can't shake this feelin', 1981; SR-27823; Spinners (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27824. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 19318; A-side Matrix # STA 814801 A SP 0-1 SM1-1 M1
        - Spinners - Love connection (raise the window down), 1981; SR-27824; Spinners (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27823. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 304; A-side Matrix # STDM 40454-2 1-1
        - Spinners - Mighty love, 1974; SR-27825; Spinners (Box 70)
          Catalog # SD 7296; A-side Matrix # ST-A-743049-F F-RE 4 AS 78742 PR
        - Spinners - The Rubberband Man, 1976; SR-27826; Spinners (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27827. Different discs.
          Catalog # DSKO 76; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-32279-32 (PR)
        - Reflections - Gift wrap my love, 1976; SR-27827; Reflections (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27826. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-8542; A-side Matrix # (93231-A) PRO-8542-H-1 Jay Luck
        - Spinners - Spinners live! (disc one), 1975; SR-27828; Spinners (Box 70)
          Catalog # SD 2-910; A-side Matrix # ST-A-753501-B B-1-11 PRC
        - Spinners - Dancin' and lovin', 1979; SR-27829; Spinners (Box 70)
          Catalog # SD 19256; A-side Matrix # STA 794379-A 0-2 (PR) SP
        - Spizzles - Spikey dream flowers, 1981; SR-27830; Spizzles (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27831. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-4861; A-side Matrix # T1 AM SP 04861-A T3 A3
        - Spizzles - Spikey dream flowers, 1981; SR-27831; Spizzles (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27830. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-4861; A-side Matrix # T1 AM SP 04861-A T3 A6
        - Splendor - Splendor, 1979; SR-27832; Splendor (Box 70)
          Catalog # JC 35798; A-side Matrix # PAL 35798-1C
        - Splendor - All night long, 1979; SR-27833; Splendor (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27834. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 23-10946; A-side Matrix # XSP-165741-1C
        - Splendor - All night long, 1979; SR-27834; Splendor (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27833. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 23-10946; A-side Matrix # XSS 165742-1C
        - Spoon Wizard - Pantaloon, 1999; SR-27835; Spoon Wizard (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27836. Different discs.
          Catalog # FB001; A-side Matrix # Tun D Masterpiece FB-001 A
        - Spoon Wizard - Me & Spoonice, 2001; SR-27836; Spoon Wizard (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27835. Different discs.
          Catalog # FB005; A-side Matrix # 08 45288 20 1A1 FB 005 Tun D
        - Spoon Wizard - Shoe monkey, 2000; SR-27837; Spoon Wizard (Box 70)
          Catalog # FB002; A-side Matrix # FB002-A Tun D Masterpiece 08 43254 20 1A1
        - Spoonie Gee - The godfather of rap, 1987; SR-27838; Spoonie Gee (Box 70)
          Catalog # TUF LP5551; A-side Matrix # TUF LP 5551-A
        - Spoonie Gee - Godfather of hip hop, 1996; SR-27839; Spoonie Gee (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27840. Different discs.
          Catalog # OSF LP 4014; A-side Matrix # OSF LP-4014-A RE THE GODFATHER OF HIP HOP
        - Spoonie Gee - Godfather of hip hop, 1996; SR-27840; Spoonie Gee (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27839. Different discs. Test pressing
        - Spoons - Stick figure neighborhood, 1981; SR-27841; Spoons (Box 70)
          Catalog # LR 012; A-side Matrix # LR-012-A-2 ''ARRIVAL'' TZC-A RE1
          Ready Records
        - Sporty Thieves - Thieven' beatz; Back dat ass up!, 2000; SR-27842; Sporty Thieves; Stik-E & The Hoodz (Box 70)
          Catalog # WL 12; A-side Matrix # WL-12-A RE F/W GSV
        - Spy - Spy, 1980; SR-27843; Spy (Box 70)
          Catalog # NJZ 36378; A-side Matrix # AL-36378-1H
          Kirshner
        - Spyro Gyra - Morning dance, 1979; SR-27844; Spyro Gyra (Box 70)
          Catalog # INF-9004; A-side Matrix # INS-9004-A-Md-1
          Infinity Records
        - Squeeze - Tempted, 1981; SR-27845; Squeeze (Box 70)
          Catalog # SP-17158; A-side Matrix # S AM SP 017158-A-S2
        - SSQ - Synthicide, 1984; SR-27846; SSQ (Box 70)
          Catalog # SPRO-9072; A-side Matrix # O SPRO-1-9072-Z1
        - St. Paul - St. Paul, 1987; SR-27847; St. Paul (Box 70)
          Catalog # MCA-42060; A-side Matrix # T1 MCA 7084 594
        - Stainless Steal - More than meets the eye; It all comes down to love, 1978; SR-27848; Stainless Steal (Box 70)
          Catalog # WBSD 8829; A-side Matrix # WBSD-8829 WAA-8456-S M-1 V 24309 2
        - Five Stairsteps - The Stairsteps, 1971; SR-27849; Five Stairsteps (Box 70)
          Catalog # BDS 5079; A-side Matrix # BDA 5079 A-2 RE Soe SON
        - Standing Waves - Vertigo, 1981; SR-27850; Standing Waves (Box 70)
          Catalog # CR 006; A-side Matrix # SW-001-A NR 13339-I
          Classified Records
          Austin, Texas
        - Stanley, Pamala - This is hot, 1979; SR-27851; Stanley, Pamala (Box 70)
          Catalog # SW-17011; A-side Matrix # SW-1-17011 Z10
        - Stansfield, Lisa - Affection, 1989; SR-27852; Stansfield, Lisa (Box 70)
          Catalog # 210 379; A-side Matrix # 020 5 210 379 A-1
        - Staple Singers - The best of the Staple Singers, 1974; SR-27853; Staple Singers (Box 70)
          Catalog # STS-5523; A-side Matrix # STXS-1002-5 SS-0651-R -L NIX-
          Stax
        - Staples - Unlock your mind, 1978; SR-27854; Staples (Box 70)
          Catalog # BSK 3192; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3192 LW1
        - Staples, Mavis - Tonight I feel like dancing, 1979; SR-27855; Staples, Mavis (Box 70)
          Catalog # WBSD 8837; A-side Matrix # WBSD-8837-WAL-0323-S-S1 24351 1
        - Staples, Mavis - Time waits for no one, 1989; SR-27856; Staples, Mavis (Box 70)
          Catalog # 1-25798; A-side Matrix # 1-25798-A-SH-1 B-34975-SH1 24694 1-1
        - Star, Ian - Free bird; A better way, 1990; SR-27857; Star, Ian (Box 70)
          Catalog # MSP 1001; A-side Matrix # MSP 1001 F/W RCE
          Zericote Records
        - Stardive - Stardive, 1974; SR-27858; Stardive (Box 70)
          Catalog # KC 33047; A-side Matrix # P AL 33047-1A
        - Stardom Groove - It's too late (for love), 1986; SR-27859; Stardom Groove; Wynne, Tonya (Box 70)
          Catalog # NYG 1000; A-side Matrix # HERbIE JR NYG-1000-A-RE
          New York Groove Records
          Flushing, New York
        - Stargard - The changing of the gard, 1979; SR-27860; Stargard (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27861. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BSK 3386; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3386 SP-1 1-2 AZ
        - Stargard - The changing of the gard, 1979; SR-27861; Stargard (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27860. 2 copies.
        - Starpoint - Wanting you, 1981; SR-27862; Starpoint (Box 70)
          Catalog # CCLP 2020; A-side Matrix # CCLP-2020-AS-PW HW (PR)
          Chocolate City
        - Starpoint - Hot to the touch, 1988; SR-27863; Starpoint (Box 70)
          Catalog # 60810-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60810 A DMM 1 SP1-1 STERLING-2
        - Starpoint - Restless, 1985; SR-27864; Starpoint (Box 70)
          Catalog # 60424-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60424 A 2 1-3
        - Starpoint - Keep on it, 1981; SR-27865; Starpoint (Box 70)
          Catalog # CCLP 2018; A-side Matrix # CCLP-2018-AS-PW (PR)
        - Starr - Signed & sealed, 1985; SR-27866; Starr (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27867. 2 copies.
          Catalog # D-246; A-side Matrix # HerbIE JR A- D-246 A
          Starlite
          Westbury, New York
        - Starr - Signed & sealed, 1985; SR-27867; Starr (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27866. 2 copies.
        - Starr, Edwin - 25 Miles, 1969; SR-27868; Starr, Edwin (Box 70)
          Catalog # GLPS-940; A-side Matrix # HS-1588-4 X 4RS-2710-1 GLPS-940 INK
          Gordy
        - Starr, Maurice - Flaming Starr, 1980; SR-27869; Starr, Maurice (Box 70)
          Catalog # AFL1-3638; A-side Matrix # AFL1 3638A 1 I
        - Stars On - Stars On 45 III; Rollin' stars, 1982; SR-27870; Stars On (Box 70)
          Catalog # DMD 335; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40927-1 Gt9P SP 1-1 SM1-1
        - Staton, Candi - Chance, 1979; SR-27871; Staton, Candi (Box 70)
          Catalog # BSK 3333; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3333-LW2
        - Steady B - Bring the beat back, 1986; SR-27872; Steady B (Box 70)
          Catalog # 1020-1-J; A-side Matrix # A 1 1020 1 JA-1
        - Steady B - What's my name, 1987; SR-27873; Steady B (Box 70)
          Catalog # 1060-1-J; A-side Matrix # 1060-1-JA F/W Ȼ
        - Steinski and Mass Media - It's up to you, 1992; SR-27874; Steinski and Mass Media (Box 70)
          Catalog # ZEN 1211; A-side Matrix # RAYS ZEN-1211-A-1 BC2278
          Ninja Tune
        - Steps - Deeper shade of blue, 2000; SR-27875; Steps (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27876. 2 copies.
          Catalog # STEPSDEEPER2; A-side Matrix # STEPSDEEPER-2-A1 TRANSFERMATION MA
          Zomba Records Ltd.
        - Steps - Deeper shade of blue, 2000; SR-27876; Steps (Box 70)
          In same jacket as # SR-27875. 2 copies.
          Catalog # STEPSDEEPER2; A-side Matrix # STEPS DEEPER-2-A1 TRANSFERMATION MA
        - Sterling, Michael - No such animal, 1987; SR-27877; Sterling, Michael (Box 70)
          Catalog # MRI-2000; A-side Matrix # MRO-1000-A STERLINGPLATINUM JUYC-2 A THE STERLING TOUCH
          Magnum Records International
        - Stetsasonic - Talkin' all that Jazz, 1988; SR-27878; Stetsasonic (Box 71)
          Catalog # TB 918 A; A-side Matrix # TB-918-A F/W HERbIE JR
          Tommy Boy
        - Steven & Sterling - Can I be with you tonight, 1982; SR-27879; Steven & Sterling (Box 71)
          Catalog # JT-13311; A-side Matrix # PD-13311-A 2S TM1-S
        - Stevens, Clive - Brainchild, 1981; SR-27880; Stevens, Clive (Box 71)
          Catalog # GR 1843; A-side Matrix # GR-1843-A-1
          Guerrilla Records & Tapes
        - Stewart, Jermaine - Say it again, 1987; SR-27881; Stewart, Jermaine (Box 71)
          Catalog # AL-8455; A-side Matrix # AL-8455-SA-RE-1 ELS-1 EMW
        - Stewart, Rod - Blondes have more fun, 1978; SR-27882; Stewart, Rod (Box 71)
          Catalog # BSK-3261; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3261 JW4 #2
        - Stone City Band - Meet the Stone City Band! - out from the shadow, 1983; SR-27883; Stone City Band (Box 71)
          Catalog # 6042GL; A-side Matrix # 6042-GL-A-15A ZLT #13 001 BPR
        - Storm - Storm, 1979; SR-27884; Storm (Box 71)
          Catalog # MCA-3179; A-side Matrix # MCA-1945-1-SS2
        - Strafe - Comin' from another place, 1985; SR-27885; Strafe (Box 71)
          Catalog # SP-12152; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012152-A-ES1 HERbIE JR
        - Stranglers - Dreamtime, 1986; SR-27886; Stranglers (Box 71)
          Catalog # E 40607; A-side Matrix # AL-40607-1F G1 B5
        - Streek - Streek, 1981; SR-27887; Streek (Box 71)
          Catalog # FC 37660; A-side Matrix # 0 PAL-37660 1-J
        - Street Players - Dancin' fever, 1979; SR-27888; Street Players (Box 71)
          Catalog # SW-50071; A-side Matrix # SW-50071-AS CP-2 AZ
          Ariola Records America
        - Strike Boys - The rhyme, 1998; SR-27889; Strike Boys (Box 71)
          Catalog # WALLT 041; A-side Matrix # WALL T 041-A1 SIMON THE EXCHANGE
          London, England
        - Strikers - The Strikers, 1981; SR-27890; Strikers (Box 71)
          Catalog # PRL 14100 AS; A-side Matrix # PRL-14100-A HERbIE CS FK
        - Strikers - Body music, 1981; SR-27891; Strikers (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27892. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL D 608; A-side Matrix # P RLD-608 AS-1A RJ/FR BCS NYC
        - Strikers - Body music, 1981; SR-27892; Strikers (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27891. 2 copies.
        - Stroke - Stroke, 1985; SR-27893; Stroke (Box 71)
          Catalog # 90296-1; A-side Matrix # ST-OM-855757 A 1-1
          Omni Records
        - Stuff - Stuff it!, 1979; SR-27894; Stuff (Box 71)
          Catalog # BSK 3262; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3262 JW1 #3
        - Style - Telephone, 1985; SR-27895; Style (Box 71)
          Catalog # 0-20328; A-side Matrix # 0 20328A SH2 O B-21003-SH2 SLM 9315 1-1
        - Style - In tone we trust, 1990; SR-27896; Style (Box 71)
          Catalog # SEL 21637; A-side Matrix # SEL 21637 A 1A G1 F/W (M) B
        - Style Posse - No rhyme or reason; Something good, 1988; SR-27897; Style Posse (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27898. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NS-102; A-side Matrix # S-19224
          Recess
          Minneapolis, Minnesota
        - Style Posse - No rhyme or reason; Something good, 1988; SR-27898; Style Posse (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27897. 2 copies.
        - Stylistics - Hurry up this way again, 1980; SR-27899; Stylistics (Box 71)
          Catalog # JZ 36470; A-side Matrix # PIR AL-36470-1A F/WNS
        - Stylistics - 1982, 1982; SR-27900; Stylistics (Box 71)
          Catalog # FZ 37955; A-side Matrix # PIR AL-37955-1G F/WNS
        - Stylistics - Closer than close, 1981; SR-27901; Stylistics (Box 71)
          Catalog # FZ 37458; A-side Matrix # PIR AL-37458-1A F/WNS
        - Stylistics - Round 2, 1972; SR-27902; Stylistics (Box 71)
          Catalog # AV-11006-598; A-side Matrix # AVCO LP-AV 11-6 A F/W S
          Avco Records
        - Stylistics - Heavy, 1974; SR-27903; Stylistics (Box 71)
          Catalog # AV-69004-698; A-side Matrix # G KONG AV 69-4 A-1 2
        - Suavé - Don't rush, 1988; SR-27904; Suavé (Box 71)
          Catalog # V-15394; A-side Matrix # V-1-15394-10106B/C/D-Z1 FUTURE DISC
        - Suavé - I'm your playmate, 1988; SR-27905; Suavé (Box 71)
          Catalog # C1-48686; A-side Matrix # B-29938-RE-1-G1 C1-1-48686-RE1- G1 20036 1-1
        - Sue Saad And The Next - Sue Saad And The Next, 1980; SR-27906; Sue Saad And The Next (Box 71)
          Catalog # P-4; A-side Matrix # P4-A 1AR TM1-X B-14651
        - Sugar Daddy - Another one bites the dust, 1980; SR-27907; Sugar Daddy (Box 71)
          Catalog # OW001; A-side Matrix # OW-001-A FW HERB Hi KEVIN KEEP SPINING
          One Way Records
        - Sugarfoot - Sugar ''kiss'', 1985; SR-27908; Sugarfoot (Box 71)
          Catalog # 1-25168; A-side Matrix # 1-2516 8 A RE-1 SR-2 LH
        - Sugarhill Gang - 8th Wonder, 1981; SR-27909; Sugarhill Gang (Box 71)
          Catalog # SH-249; A-side Matrix # VID-306
        - Sugarhill Gang - Sugarhill Gang, 1980; SR-27910; Sugarhill Gang (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27911. Different discs.
          Catalog # SH-245; A-side Matrix # V1A-1-RE
        - Grandmaster Flash - They said it couldn't be done, 1985; SR-27911; Grandmaster Flash (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27910. Different discs.
          Catalog # 60389-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60389-A-1
        - Suicide - Suicide: Alan Vega-Martin Rev, 1980; SR-28825; Suicide (Box 71)
          Catalog # AN 7080; A-side Matrix # AN 7080A-1A
          Antilles
        - Summer, Donna - Cats without claws, 1984; SR-27912; Summer, Donna (Box 71)
          Catalog # GHS 24040; A-side Matrix # 6HS-24040-A RE-1 SR2 -5 FUTURE DISC
        - Summer, Donna - Bad girls (disc one), 1979; SR-27913; Summer, Donna (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27914. Double album.
          Catalog # NBLP-2-7150; A-side Matrix # T1 NBLP-2-7150-AS-RE-2 T3 AZ
        - Summer, Donna - Bad girls (disc two), 1979; SR-27914; Summer, Donna (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27913. Double album.
          Catalog # NBLP-2-7150; A-side Matrix # T1 NBLP-2-7150-CS-RE-2 TH-1 AZ
        - Summer, Donna - All systems go, 1987; SR-27915; Summer, Donna (Box 71)
          Catalog # GHS 24102; A-side Matrix # GHS-24102-A SH-1 O B-28458-SH1 17523 1-
        - Summer, Donna - Hot stuff; Bad girls, 1979; SR-27916; Summer, Donna (Box 71)
          Catalog # NBD 20167 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20167-AS CP2 AZ
        - Summers, Bill - Feel the heat, 1977; SR-27917; Summers, Bill (Box 71)
          Catalog # P-10102; A-side Matrix # P 10102 (RE-2)-A P
          Prestige
        - Summers, Bill - On sunshine, 1979; SR-27918; Summers, Bill; Summers Heat (Box 71)
          Catalog # P-10107; A-side Matrix # P-10107-A-RE 1A
        - Summers, Bill - Straight to the bank, 1978; SR-27919; Summers, Bill; Summers Heat (Box 71)
          Catalog # P-10105; A-side Matrix # P10105 A KE-DUN-A
        - Summers, Bill - Seventeen, 1982; SR-27920; Summers, Bill; Summers Heat (Box 71)
          Catalog # MCA-5367; A-side Matrix # MCA-3191-W5 MCASh
        - Summers, Bill - Jam the box, 1981; SR-27921; Summers, Bill; Summers Heat (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27922. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MCA-5266; A-side Matrix # MCA-2755-W1 MCASh
        - Summers, Bill - Jam the box, 1981; SR-27922; Summers, Bill; Summers Heat (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27921. 2 copies.
        - Sun - Eclipse, 1984; SR-27923; Sun (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27924. 2 copies.
          Catalog # A-401-SN-LP; A-side Matrix # 402034X-A OCO TD
          Air City Records
          Dayton, Ohio
        - Sun - Eclipse, 1984; SR-27924; Sun (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27923. 2 copies.
        - Sun - Destination: Sun, 1979; SR-27925; Sun (Box 71)
          Catalog # ST-11941; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11941 G-10 Waimu
        - Sun - I want your love, 1980; SR-27926; Sun (Box 71)
          Catalog # SPRO-9530; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9530-96912-Z 2
        - Sun - Space ranger (majic's in the air), 1980; SR-27927; Sun (Box 71)
          Catalog # SPRO-9398; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9398 (96907-A) Z5
        - Sun - Force of nature, 1981; SR-27928; Sun (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27929. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ST-12142; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12142 F-2 Wavy
        - Sun - Force of nature, 1981; SR-27929; Sun (Box 71)
          In same jacket as # SR-27928. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ST-12142; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12142 F-2 #6 Wavy
        - Sun, Moon & Star - Ghetto child; Don't sell out, 1991; SR-27930; Sun, Moon & Star (Box 71)
          Catalog # MR-50003; A-side Matrix # MR 50003-Y-RE
          Moonroof Records
        - Sunrize - Sunrize, 1982; SR-27931; Sunrize (Box 71)
          Catalog # NB-33257-1; A-side Matrix # NB-AL-33257-1 GD-2
          The Boardwalk Entertainment Co
        - Sunshine - Sunshine, 1977; SR-27932; Sunshine (Box 72)
          Catalog # SR 3018; A-side Matrix # RSD-627-A-RE BEST
          Roulette
        - Supa Technics - Serious beats, 1998; SR-27934; Supa Technics (Box 72)
          Catalog # BB-200; A-side Matrix # BB200-9903X25-A A+R SP6D
          Baltimore Breakbeat Records
        - Super Diamono De Dakar - People, 1987; SR-27935; Super Diamono De Dakar (Box 72)
          Catalog # ENC 139; A-side Matrix # MPO I ENC 135 A
          Encore !
        - Super Diamono De Dakar - Mam', 1985; SR-27936; Super Diamono De Dakar (Box 72)
          Catalog # 8011; A-side Matrix # CEL-8011 A YD
          Phil' One Records
        - Super Lover Cee & Casanova Rud - Girls I got 'em locked, 1988; SR-27937; Super Lover Cee & Casanova Rud (Box 72)
          Catalog # 60807-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60807A-2 1-2
        - Super Lover Cee & Casanova Rud - Girls I got 'em locked, 1988; SR-27938; Super Lover Cee & Casanova Rud (Box 72)
          Catalog # ED 5318; A-side Matrix # 1-2 ST-ED-66752 A-1 cg
          DNA International Records
        - Supercharge - I think I'm gonna fall (in love), 1978; SR-27939; Supercharge (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27940. 2 copies.
          Catalog # VS 20212; A-side Matrix # VS20212-A SNB-BK
          St. Laurent, Quebec, Canada
        - Supercharge - I think I'm gonna fall (in love), 1978; SR-27940; Supercharge (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27939. 2 copies.
        - Superdense Child - Elvis pig farmer (disc one), 2001; SR-27941; Superdense Child (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27942. Double album.
          Catalog # MARLP005; A-side Matrix # MARLP005 A-01-1- SUPER DUPER! B SIMON THE EXCHANGE
          Marble Bar
        - Superdense Child - Elvis pig farmer (disc two), 2001; SR-27942; Superdense Child (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27941. Double album.
          Catalog # MARLP005; A-side Matrix # MARLP005 C-01-1- SUPER COOL! B SIMON THE EXCHANGE
        - Supermax - Fly with me, 1979; SR-27943; Supermax (Box 72)
          Catalog # 6E-193; A-side Matrix # 1-1 CE 193 A-SP
        - Superior Movement - Be my cinderella; For you, 1981; SR-27944; Superior Movement (Box 72)
          Catalog # AS 1322; A-side Matrix # XSM1688852-1A
          Chycago International Music (C.I.M)
        - Supersempfft - Out of time, 1979; SR-27945; Supersempfft (Box 72)
          Catalog # CBS 12.7401; A-side Matrix # CBS 12-7401 A SST
        - Supply & Demand - Chronic 17 (disc one), 2001; SR-27946; Supply & Demand (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27947. Double album.
          Catalog # CHR-017; A-side Matrix # CHRONIC-17-A1 JB Sto
          Chronic
        - Supply & Demand - Chronic 17 (disc two), 2001; SR-27947; Supply & Demand (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27946. Double album.
          Catalog # CHR-017; A-side Matrix # CHRONIC-17-C1 JB
        - Sutton, Mike & Sutton, Brenda - Don't hold back, 1982; SR-27948; Sutton, Mike & Sutton, Brenda (Box 72)
          Catalog # SAM 704; A-side Matrix # SAM 704-1
        - Suzy Q - Get on up and do it again, 1981; SR-27949; Suzy Q (Box 72)
          Catalog # SD 19328; A-side Matrix # STA-814811-A 0-1 SM1-3 SP
        - Swamp Dogg - Have you heard this story??, 1974; SR-27950; Swamp Dogg (Box 72)
          Catalog # ILPS 9299; A-side Matrix # ILPS-9299-A
        - Swampgas - Swampgas, 1972; SR-27951; Swampgas (Box 72)
          Catalog # BDS 5102; A-side Matrix # BDS-5102-A-2 SON
        - Sweat Band - Sweat Band, 1980; SR-27952; Sweat Band (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27953. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JZ 36857; A-side Matrix # PAL-36857-2C
          Uncle Jam
        - Sweat Band - Sweat Band, 1980; SR-27953; Sweat Band (Box 72)
          In same jacket as # SR-27952. 2 copies.